<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:openSearch='http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/' xmlns:gsx='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006/extended'><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>sessions</title><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/pub?key=0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE'/><link rel='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005#feed' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic'/><author><name>m.kupriyanov</name><email>m.kupriyanov@googlemail.com</email></author><openSearch:totalResults>29</openSearch:totalResults><openSearch:startIndex>1</openSearch:startIndex><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/cokwr</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 2</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 10:45-11:45, room: 1, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Being Epic: Best Practice for Building Android Apps, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Reto Meier, sessionabstract: Turn good ideas into great apps by following some essential Android development best practices. Starting with an overview of the 5 deadly sins and 5 golden rules, you will learn how to build apps that users love and that are good citizens of the mobile environment. You will also learn specific best practices for background apps and location based services., sessionrequirements: Proficiency in Java and a solid grasp of Android's fundamental concepts, sessionlink: being-epic-best-practice-for-building-android-apps, sessionhashtag: #android1</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/cokwr'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/cpzh4</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 3</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 12:00-13:00, room: 1, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Excellence in the Android User Experience, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Roman Nurik, sessionabstract: As Android Market approaches 100,000 apps, developers must strive to attract and retain users to stay relevant. Crafting a great user experience and user interface is fundamental in achieving this. In this talk, we'll discuss interaction and visual design tips, as well as relevant SDK resources, that can help make your apps shine., sessionrequirements: Proficiency in Java and a solid grasp of Android's fundamental concepts, sessionlink: android-user-experience-aufpoliert, sessionhashtag: #android2</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/cpzh4'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/cre1l</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 4</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 14:00-15:00, room: 1, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: What's New in the Android Developer's World, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Justin Mattson, sessionabstract: We will explore Android's ever expanding APIs and services, covering the latest developments and how they can be used to create amazing experiences for your users., sessionrequirements: Proficiency in Java and a solid grasp of Android's fundamental concepts, sessionlink: neuigkeiten-aus-der-welt-der-android-develope, sessionhashtag: #android3</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/cre1l'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/chk2m</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 5</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 15:15-16:15, room: 1, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Close to the Metal: Building with the Android NDK, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Dan Galpin, sessionabstract: Whether it's for portability or for performance, many Android developers are turning to the NDK for their applications. We will walk through building applications on NDK, explore NDK-related problems, and demonstrate 3D graphics and sound, talking specifically to developers of games and real-time applications., sessionrequirements: Proficiency in Java and a solid grasp of Android's fundamental concepts, sessionlink: close-to-the-metal-building-with-the-android-ndk, sessionhashtag: #android4</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/chk2m'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/ciyn3</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 6</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 16:30-17:30, room: 1, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Your App Can Run on Every Android Device, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Christian Kurzke, sessionabstract: We will explore Android's ever expanding APIs and services, covering the latest developments and how they can be used to create amazing experiences for your users., sessionrequirements: Proficiency in Java and a solid grasp of Android's fundamental concepts, sessionlink: apps-koennen-auf-jedem-android-funktionieren, sessionhashtag: #android5</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/ciyn3'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/ckd7g</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 7</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 17:45-18:45, room: 1, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: HTML5 or Native for Mobile Development?, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Reto Meier, Michael Mahemoff, sessionabstract: Native apps or mobile web? It's often a hard choice when deciding where to invest your mobile development resources. While the mobile web continues to grow, native apps and App Stores are incredibly popular. We will present both perspectives before answering questions in a panel style debate., sessionrequirements: none, sessionlink: html5-oder-native-for-mobile-development, sessionhashtag: #android6</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/ckd7g'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/clrrx</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 8</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 10:45-11:45, room: 2, product: Chrome &amp; HTML5, track: Chrome &amp; HTML5, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Programming the Web with Native Client, tags: Chrome, sessionspeakers: Brad Chen, sessionabstract: Native Client gives developers new programming language choices on the web. Learn how you can build rich applications with all of the safety and portability you expect from the web, while benefiting from the performance of native code. We will also show you how to access emerging capabilities on the web such as sound and 3D graphics., sessionlink: programming-the-web-with-native-client, sessionhashtag: #chrome1</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/clrrx'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/cyevm</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 9</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 12:00-13:00, room: 2, product: Chrome &amp; HTML5, track: Chrome &amp; HTML5, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Google Chrome Extensions, tags: Chrome, sessionspeakers: Paul Kinlan, sessionabstract: Google Chrome has a rich Extension API that you can take advantage of to enhance the functionality of the browser. In this session learn how to create extensions and discover some of the advanced features offered by the API's., sessionlink: tba, sessionhashtag: #chrome2</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/cyevm'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/cztg3</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 10</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 14:00-15:00, room: 2, product: Chrome &amp; HTML5, track: Chrome &amp; HTML5, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Practical HTML5, tags: Chrome, sessionspeakers: Jeremy Orlow, Malte Ubl, sessionabstract: HTML5 is the future of the web, yet a surprising amount of it can be used today. In this session, we’ll give an overview of what’s possible with HTML5 today, what’s on the horizon, and how you can use these technologies while still richly supporting legacy browsers., sessionlink: practical-html5, sessionhashtag: #chrome3</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/cztg3'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/d180g</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 11</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 15:15-16:15, room: 2, product: Chrome &amp; HTML5, track: Chrome &amp; HTML5, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Google Chrome Developer Tools, tags: Chrome, sessionspeakers: Alexei Masterov, Pavel Feldman, sessionabstract: In this session we'll give an overview of Developer Tools for Google Chrome that is a part of the standard Chrome distribution. Chrome Developer Tools allow inspecting, debugging and tuning the web applications and a lot more. In addition to this overview we would like to share some implementation details of the Developer Tools features and call for your contribution., sessionrequirements: Basic knowledge of HTML and JavaScript., sessionlink: chrome-dev-tools, sessionhashtag: #chrome4</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/d180g'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/d2mkx</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 12</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 16:30-17:30, room: 2, product: Chrome &amp; HTML5, track: Chrome &amp; HTML5, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Web Apps on the Chrome Web Store, tags: Chrome, sessionspeakers: Paul Kinlan, sessionabstract: HTML5 is the future of the web, learn how the Chrome Web Store can help you distribute and monetize your applications., sessionlink: web-apps-fuer-den-google-chrome-web-store, sessionhashtag: #chrome5</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/d2mkx'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/cssly</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 13</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 17:45-18:45, room: 2, product: Chrome &amp; HTML5, track: Chrome &amp; HTML5, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Authentication on the World Wide Web, tags: Chrome, sessionspeakers: Steven Bazyl, sessionabstract: A discussion of all the auth tangles you've encountered so far -- OpenID, SSO, 2-Legged OAuth, 3-Legged OAuth, and Hybrid OAuth. We'll show you when and where to use them, and explain how they all integrate with Google APIs and other developer products., sessionlink: authentifizierung-im-world-wide-web, sessionhashtag: #chrome6</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/cssly'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/b8lvi</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 14</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 10:45-11:45, room: 3, product: Google Web Toolkit, track: GWT, Cloud Platform, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Google Web Toolkit + VMWare, tags: App Engine, sessionspeakers: Christian Dupuis, sessionlink: google-web-toolkit, sessionhashtag: #appengine1</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/b8lvi'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/ba0fz</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 15</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 12:00-13:00, room: 3, product: App Engine, track: App Engine, Cloud Platform, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: What's New in App Engine, tags: App Engine, sessionspeakers: Fred Sauer, sessionabstract: Multi-tenancy, Channel API and MySQL and just a few of the features recently launched on the Google App Engine platform. Come take a quick dive into these features are more., sessionlink: neues-von-app-engine, sessionhashtag: #appengine2</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/ba0fz'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/bbf0c</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 16</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 14:00-15:00, room: 3, product: App Engine, track: App Engine, Enterprise, Cloud Platform, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: App Engine for Business, tags: App Engine, sessionspeakers: Patrick Chanezon, Simon Meacham, sessionabstract: Google App Engine for Business adds Enterprises features to App Engine, making it a great platform to build Enterprise Applications: Domain Console, Service Level Agreement, Paid Support, SSL for domains, and SQL support., sessionrequirements: Enterprise Developers, sessionlink: app-engine-fuer-unternehmen, sessionhashtag: #appengine3</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/bbf0c'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/bctkt</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 17</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 15:15-16:15, room: 3, product: BigQuery, Prediction APIs, track: App Engine, Cloud Platform, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Storage, Big Query und Prediction APIs, tags: App Engine, sessionspeakers: Patrick Chanezon, Simon Meacham, sessionabstract: Google Storage for Developers is a RESTful service for storing and accessing your data on Google's infrastructure. The service combines the performance and scalability of Google's cloud with advanced security and sharing capabilities. Google Storage is an entry point for using new Google Cloud services such as BigQuery (analytics) and Prediction (Machine Learning) to get more out of your data., sessionlink: storage-big-query-und-prediction-apis, sessionhashtag: #appengine4</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/bctkt'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/bpgoi</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 18</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 16:30-17:30, room: 3, product: App Engine, track: App Engine, Cloud Platform, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: What's New in Google Geo: Maps API V3 and Fusion Tables, tags: App Engine, sessionspeakers: Mano Marks, sessionabstract: In May, the Google Maps API V3 launched out of labs with new features to help with performance and customization. At the same time, Fusion Tables is growing as a platform for Geo data hosting. This session will cover the new features, and how to integrate Fusion Tables to make a powerful, customized mapping experience for your site., sessionlink: neuigkeiten-aus-google-geo-maps-api-v3-und-fusion-tables, sessionhashtag: #appengine5</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/bpgoi'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/bqv8z</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 19</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 17:45-18:45, room: 3, product: App Engine, track: App Engine, Cloud Platform, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Google Apps Marketplace: Integrate and Sell Your Cloud Apps to Google Apps Customers, tags: App Engine, sessionspeakers: Claudio Cherubino, sessionabstract: In this introductory session targeted to ISVs or SIs we'll provide an overview of the Google Apps Marketplace and discuss product and marketing best practices to monetize a cloud application., sessionlink: google-apps-marketplace-integrate-and-sell-your-cloud-apps-to-google-apps-customers, sessionhashtag: #appengine6</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/bqv8z'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/ddv49</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 20</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 10:45-11:45, room: 4, product: Enterprise, track: Monetization, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Practical Tips for Building a Web Business, tags: Enterprise, sessionspeakers: Chewy Trewhella, sessionlink: praktische-tipps-zum-aufbau-eines-web-business, sessionhashtag: #enterprise1</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/ddv49'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/d6ua4</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 21</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 15:15-16:15, room: 4, product: Enterprise, track: Monetization, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Making Money with Google Ad Tools, tags: Enterprise, sessionspeakers: Julian Toledo, sessionabstract: This session will introduce you to Google's powerful AdWords advertising platform and explore some of the ways developers can drive traffic to their apps with creative, automated advertising. In addition to AdWords fundamentals, we'll review use cases for the API and best practices for getting started., sessionlink: geld-verdienen-mit-google-ad-tools, sessionhashtag: #googleadtools</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/d6ua4'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/d88ul</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 22</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 16:30-17:30, room: 4, product: Enterprise, track: Monetization, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: VC investement for your company, tags: Enterprise, sessionspeakers: Don Dodge, sessionabstract: How can you raise Venture Capital money for your startup? Hear from professional investors and experienced founders who have raised money., sessionlink: vc-ange, sessionhashtag: #angel</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/d88ul'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/dkvya</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 23</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 17:45-18:45, room: 4, product: Enterprise, track: Monetization, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Mobile Monetization, tags: Enterprise, sessionspeakers: Russell Buckley, sessionabstract: This session will explore strategies for making money from Android Apps, from advertising to subscriptions. We’ll look at case studies which discuss earning potential, as well as techniques for maximising income., sessionlink: mobile-monetization, sessionhashtag: mobilemonetization</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/dkvya'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/dnp34</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 24</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 12:00-13:00, room: 4, product: Enterprise, track: Social Web, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Google Buzz API, tags: Enterprise, sessionspeakers: Chris Chabot, sessionabstract: Having a social profile online is as common as having a mobile phone, The Web is becoming a social place. It is moving from a static place to one about people sharing experiences, playing, working and talking together. However many of these social destinations speak different languages (protocols). Rather than inventing a new language, Google utilizes existing standards to avoid such headaches In this session we'll look at these open standards and the Google Buzz API and show you how to build a web application using this platform., sessionrequirements: A positive attitude and a taste for the social web, sessionlink: google-buzz-api, sessionhashtag: #buzzapi</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/dnp34'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/dp3nl</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 25</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 14:00-15:00, room: 4, product: Enterprise, track: Social Web, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Exploring Google's Social APIs, tags: Enterprise, sessionspeakers: Ade Oshineye, sessionabstract: This session is a deep dive into the Buzz APIs. We'll explore their usage and look at the different kinds of services and applications you can build using our social platform. Afterwards you'll be able to use Google's Social APIs to make your products better., sessionrequirements: Proficiency in Python and an understanding of HTTP, sessionlink: googles-social-apis-entdecken, sessionhashtag: #socialapi</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/dp3nl'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/djhdx</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 26</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 10:45-11:45, room: 5, product: Tech Talks, track: Tech Talks, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Overview of Google's APIs, tags: Tech Talks, sessionspeakers: Dr. Jens Trapp, Malte Ubl, sessionlink: ueberblick-google-apis, sessionhashtag: #googleapi</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/djhdx'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/dw4je</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 27</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 12:00-13:00, room: 5, product: Tech Talks, track: Tech Talks, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: What We Have Learned: Google Maps API Best Practices, tags: Tech Talks, sessionspeakers: Martin Kleppe, sessionabstract: What We Have Learned - Google Maps API Best Practices How do we process thousands of geo data in our browser? Which design is best for your app? How can you optimize performance on mobile devices? Hacks &amp; Tweaks: Martin Kleppe shows how to combine different components of the Google Maps API effectively, using real-world examples., sessionlink: was-wir-bisher-gelernt-haben-google-maps-api-best-practices, sessionhashtag: #googlemaps</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/dw4je'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/dxj3v</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 28</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 14:00-15:00, room: 5, product: Tech Talks, track: Tech Talks, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Building a social web using Google Friend Connect and OpenSocial, tags: Tech Talks, sessionspeakers: Nenad Nikolic, sessionlink: building-a-social-web-using-google-friend-connect-and-opensocial, sessionhashtag: #opensocial</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/dxj3v'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/dyxo8</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 29</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 15:15-16:15, room: 5, product: Tech Talks, track: Tech Talks, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Real World Website Performance Optimization, tags: Tech Talks, sessionspeakers: Malte Ubl, sessionabstract: Website performance has sprung up as one of the most exciting topics in web development with strong research showing that optimizing performance can create real business value while also creating interesting challenges for us, the developer community. This talk will be devided into two main parts: 1. How can I persuade my boss to invest into high performance websites. We'll look at real world data and how that applies to your businness (Don't worry it won't be boring :) 2. A look at different performance optimization strategies and tips and tricks how to apply these to your website and your software development process., sessionlink: real-world-website-performance-optimization</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/dyxo8'/></entry><entry><id>https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/e0c8p</id><updated>2010-10-31T14:42:14.856Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 30</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: 09.11.2010, sessiontime: 16:30-17:30, room: 5, product: Tech Talks, track: Tech Talks, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Writing HTML5 apps with Google App Engine, Google Closure Library and Clojure, tags: Tech Talks, sessionspeakers: Stefan Richter, sessionabstract: Welcome back to the world of client-side applications! With HTML5 you are able to build a client that runs inside the web-browser on your desktop machine. Frankly, this is much more difficult than writing classic internet-style server-side apps. And it is much more difficult than writing standard GUI desktop apps. How do you structure such an app? How to write a large piece of software in JavaScript? How to use the Cloud to build an app that scales over large sets of data and enables lots of users to cooperate over the internet? And how to make this adventure a real pleasure?! We will together dive into some real-world examples and provoking thought-experiments., sessionlink: writing-html5-apps-with-google-app-engine</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='https://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/0Akgh73WhU1qHdHJmSUlSb0JIckowX1ZiQkhsYmdkdkE/od6/public/basic/e0c8p'/></entry></feed>